https://www.catholichealthservices.org/about/privacy-policy/

Aquatic Therapy
Every Rehabilitation Hospital features an indoor temperature controlled Aquatic Center.
Learn More
Stroke Rehabiliation Programs
We provide comprehensive inpatient and outpatient programs for those suffering from stroke.
Learn More
Ranked Top 10%
Ranked within the top 10%
among 800 rehabilitation hospitals in the US by USD.
Care Transitions
To help patients manage transitions from hospital to home.
Learn More
Why Home Health
Nationally recognized in the top 10%.
View FAQ's
Home Health Team
Interdisciplinary home health team working together with patients, families and physicians.
Why Assisted Living
To handle the special needs of senior citizens in South Florida.
View FAQ's
Services
To provide personalized care for each of our residents.
View Services
Locations
Learn more about our locations in Broward and Miami-Dade.
Why Elderly Housing
Award-winning housing for seniors in South Florida.
Learn More
Locations
Located in Broward and Miami-Dade.
View Locations
Our Team
Currently operating 16 apartment complexes in South Florida.
About Catholic Hospice
Provides responsive end of life care to patients in South Florida.
Learn More
Events
Come take a look at our upcoming events.
View Events
Donate
Pay tribute to someone who has touched your life.
Centro Mater Foundation
What MATERs Most.
Learn More
History and Mission
Designed to give children a beginning foundation of success.
Learn More
Health and Nutritional Services
Provides a full range of assistance to children and families.
Catholic Health Services Privacy Policy
Catholic Health Services (“CHS”, “we”, or “us”) operates the web site located at https://www.catholichealthservices.org (the “Site”). This serves as the Privacy Policy for the Site and CHS events.
CHS makes the Site and various offers related to CHS and/or the Site available to those individuals who register directly with the Site or at CHS events (“Registrants”), subject to this Privacy Policy (the “Policy”). This Policy explains what information CHS collects about its Registrants, how CHS uses and/or shares this information, and how such information is maintained. By visiting the Site, or by registering on the Site, you signify your acceptance of this Policy.
Note that this Policy applies only with respect to the information collected by CHS and not any information collected or obtained through other methods or sources.
Collection of Personally Identifiable Information
CHS collects Registrants’ personally identifiable information (“PII”) that is volunteered by Registrants during the registration process or in response to specific information requests explicitly presented to Registrants. Examples of PII that may be requested and/or collected include: first and last name, title, address, email address, telephone number, gender, age, education, and household income. From time to time CHS may also present opportunities for Registrants to voluntarily provide additional information about themselves. CHS video records and photographs its events for posting on the Site and other sites. Registrants at events are recorded in those videos and photographs.
Use and Sharing of PII
CHS reserves the right to use Registrant PII: (1) for the specific purpose for which such information was provided, for example on the Site, in order to be a subscriber to the CHS email newsletter; (2) as disclosed at the time such information is provided; and/or (3) as disclosed in this Policy. However, please note that CHS may change this Policy at any time (See “Changes to this Policy,” below), and that therefore CHS may in the future use Registrant PII for additional purposes not currently included in this Policy.
Registrant PII collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future marketing purposes. By using the Site, you agree that you may be contacted in any manner contemplated in this section even if your number is found on a do not call registry, in-house list or similar registry.
From time to time CHS contracts with third parties to conduct marketing promotions, sweepstakes and other promotions. The PII collected from such promotions may be used for any purpose disclosed in this policy or in the rules to the specific promotion.
CHS may share Registrant PII in aggregate, non-personal form, with select companies that wish to reach a particular Registrant target audience.
CHS may disclose Registrant PII in order to: (1) comply with applicable laws (including, without limitation, the CAN-SPAM Act); (2) respond to governmental inquiries; (3) comply with valid legal process; and (4) protect the rights or property of CHS, including without limitation, filing copyright applications with the Library of Congress, Copyright Office.
CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS: YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS
California Civil Code Section 1798.83, requires companies that collect PII from California residents and disclose such information to third parties (including affiliated entities) for marketing purposes to allow California residents to provide a mechanism by which a consumer may opt-out of having his/her information shared with third parties. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request to opt-out of having your PII shared with third parties, please submit your request in writing to:
Catholic Health Services
4790 North State Road 7
Lauderdale Lakes, FL 33319
Non-Personally Identifiable Information
CHS also collects certain non-personally identifiable information, including the non-personally identifiable information more fully described below.
Cookies
CHS may use “cookies” on the Site. Cookies are small pieces of information that CHS’s server places on an individual’s computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with the Site. For example, CHS may place a cookie on a Registrant’s computer when he/she initially clicks on a link in an email from CHS. The next time that Registrant opens an email from CHS and clicks on the link, CHS’s server will recognize the cookie (and the Registrant) and allow the Registrant to perform certain actions immediately without signing in.
While some Web browsers allow a Registrant to automatically reject all cookies or be notified when a cookie is about to be placed on the Registrant’s computer, disabling this feature may compromise the efficiency and added services that cookies provide.
IP Address
CHS collects your IP (Internet Protocol) address to help diagnose problems with its server, and to administer the Site and CHS email offers. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. Your IP address is also used to help identify you during a particular session and to gather broad demographic data.
Although the information collected through the foregoing methods does not itself contain any PII, CHS may analyze and match such information with other information that you provide (including PII) as well as information that CHS may obtain elsewhere, and CHS may share all or some of such information with CHS may also disclose non-personally identifiable information in order to (1) comply with applicable laws, (2) respond to governmental inquiries, (3) comply with valid legal process, or (4) protect the rights or property of CHS or its Registrants and users of the Site.
Opt-Out of CHS Media Promotions
During registration, Registrants will have the option to not receive promotional offers and updates, via emails, from CHS and our partners. In order to not receive such promotional offers and updates, Registrants must elect that option, where indicated.
If a Registrant chooses to receive promotional offers and updates, Registrant may, at any time thereafter, choose to discontinue receiving promotional emails from CHS or the Site by following the “unsubscribe” instructions in the applicable email. Notwithstanding the foregoing, CHS may continue to contact Registrants for the purpose of communicating information about their registration with CHS or similar information relating to CHS, the Site or their registration, as well as to facilitate, complete or confirm any transaction that Registrants enter into or in response to or fulfillment of Registrants’ inquiries or requests.
Access to Information
If you want to review, correct or change your Registrant account information, please contact us at the address listed below.
Third Party Services
Certain information and services available to Registrants are provided by entities not affiliated with CHS. Although CHS advises all of its partners to support this Policy, CHS has no control over their information handling practices and is not responsible for any failure of such partners to adhere to this Policy.
Links from Email
CHS provides links to many of CHS’s advertiser and partner websites and other websites. If you link to any of these third party websites, this Policy will not apply to your use of, and activities on, those websites. We encourage you to read the legal notices posted on these sites, including their privacy policies. CHS shall have no responsibility or liability for your visitation to, and the data collection and use practices of, these websites.
Note Concerning Individuals 13 Years of Age And Younger
The Site, CHS emails and the content available in connection therewith, are neither intended for, nor directed to, children under the age of 13. You must be at least 13 years old to have our permission to use our websites and to provide your PII to CHS. If CHS learns that a person who is a Registrant is under the age of 13, CHS will promptly terminate that individual’s registration and delete the individual’s PII from CHS’s records. CHS will NOT knowingly distribute such information to third parties.
Security
While CHS takes reasonable precautions to safeguard information transmitted between CHS and Registrants and/or users of the Site, CHS may be unable to prevent unauthorized access to such information by third parties or inadvertent disclosure of such information. Registrants and users acknowledge this risk when communicating with CHS.
Consent to Processing
By providing PII and other information to CHS, Registrants of the Site fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and processing of such information in, and the transfer of such information to, the United States and other countries or territories, in accordance with the terms of this Policy.
Transfer in Certain Circumstances
In its sole discretion, CHS may transfer, sell or assign information collected on or about Registrants of the Site, including without limitation, PII and other Registrant provided information, to one or more third parties, as a result of the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of CHS.
Changes to This Policy
CHS may, from time to time, amend this Policy, in whole or part, in its sole discretion. Any changes to this Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised policy. By continuing to use the Network Site following any changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes.
Contact Catholic Health Services at:
Catholic Health Services
4790 FL-7
Lauderdale Lakes, FL 33319
TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE
These Terms and Conditions govern your use of catholichealthservices.org (hereinafter referred to as the “Site”), a service of Catholic Health Services, a ministry of the Archdiocese of Miami (hereinafter referred to as “Catholic Health Services”). Please read these Terms and Conditions, as they are a contract between Catholic Health Services and You.
By accessing and using the Site, You are subject to these Terms and Conditions, which may be updated from time to time without notice to You. You are advised to check for updates periodically. Your use of the Site reflects your agreement to be bound by these Terms and Conditions.
Any information that Catholic Health Services provides on the Site, including all content or information contained within it, any Site-related service, or service or product of any third party, are provided “as is” with no representations or warranties of any kind by Catholic Health Services, either expressed or implied including, but not limited to, the implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, and noninfringement.
You assume total responsibility and risk for Your use of the Site, Site-related services, and any service or product You receive as a result of Your use of the Site.
Catholic Health Services, its affiliates, partners and sponsors are neither responsible nor liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential, special, exemplarily, punitive or other damages arising out of or relating in any way to the Site, Site-related services, and/or content or information contained within the Site.
Your sole remedy for dissatisfaction with the Site and/or Site-related services is to stop using the Site and/or those services. Catholic Health Services makes no warranties that the Site will meet Your requirements or will be uninterrupted, timely, secure or error free, that defects will be corrected, or that the Site or the server that makes it available are free of viruses or bugs or represents the full functionality, accuracy, reliability of the materials. Catholic Health Services will not be responsible or liable to You for any loss of content or material or information uploaded or transmitted through the Site.
Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so some or all of the above exclusions may not apply to You. If the limitations set forth in these Terms and Conditions are inapplicable or unenforceable for any reason, then Catholic Health Services maximum liability to You for any type of damages, regardless of the cause of action (be it in contract, tort, breach of warranty, equity or otherwise) shall be limited to $1.00 USD.
Catholic Health Services and the Site shall not be deemed to be in breach of this agreement due to any delay or failure of performance in availability of the service resulting directly or indirectly from any act of nature or any cause beyond the reasonable control of Catholic Health Services and/or the Site.
These Terms and Conditions will remain in full force and effect while you are a user of the Site at any level in existence now or in the future. Catholic Health Services reserves the right, in its sole discretion, to pursue all of its legal remedies, including but not limited to termination of Your registration with or ability to access the Site and/or any other services provided to You by Catholic Health Services even after You are no longer a User of the Site, certain provisions of these Terms and Conditions will survive.
If any provision of this agreement is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid, the parties nevertheless agree that the court should endeavor to give effect to the parties intentions as reflected in the provision, and that the other provisions of this agreement remain in full force and effect.
The Terms and Conditions and the relationship between You and Catholic Health Services and the Site shall be governed by the laws of the State of Florida without regard to its conflicts of law provisions. You and the Site agree to submit to the personal and exclusive jurisdiction of the Courts of the Fifteenth Judicial Circuit of Florida in and for Broward County or the U.S. District Court for the Southern District of Florida.  You agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any claim or cause of action arising out of related to the use of the Site or Terms and Conditions must be filed within one (1) year after such or cause of action arose or be forever barred. These Terms and Conditions as well as the Privacy Policy, which is incorporated by reference, constitute the entire agreement between you and Catholic Health Services for the use of its Site.
